export const questions1 = [
  {
    question: 'Which rocket was the first to land a man on the moon?',
    options: ['Union', 'Atlas', 'Saturn V', 'Falcon 9'],
    correctAnswer: 'Saturn V',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What rocket is used to launch satellites into Earth orbit by SpaceX?',
    options: ['Ares I', 'Falcon 9', 'RN Zenit', 'Delta IV'],
    correctAnswer: 'Falcon 9',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which country was the first to launch a rocket into space?',
    options: ['USA', 'China', 'USSR', 'India'],
    correctAnswer: 'USSR',
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the rocket used to launch NASA's space shuttles?",
    options: ['Shuttle', 'Saturn V', 'Ares I', 'Atlas'],
    correctAnswer: 'Shuttle',
  },
  {
    question: 'What missile was developed by Germany during World War II?',
    options: ['PH Saturn', 'PH Proton', 'V-2', 'Falcon Heavy'],
    correctAnswer: 'V-2',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which rocket is the primary vehicle for delivering cargo to the International Space Station (ISS)?',
    options: ['Union', 'Delta II', 'Titan IV', 'Saturn V'],
    correctAnswer: 'Union',
  },
  {
    question: 'What rocket was developed as part of the Apollo program?',
    options: ['Saturn I', 'Ares I', 'Falcon 9', 'Saturn V'],
    correctAnswer: 'Saturn V',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which rocket is the largest in history?',
    options: ['Falcon Heavy', 'Saturn V', 'H1', 'PH Proton'],
    correctAnswer: 'Saturn V',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which rocket is the mainstay of the Chinese space program?',
    options: ['Chang Zhen (Long March)', 'Union', 'Ariane 5', 'Falcon 9'],
    correctAnswer: 'Chang Zhen (Long March)',
  },
  {
    question:
      "What rocket was used for the first flights to the Earth's orbit?",
    options: ['Saturn V', 'Shuttle', 'Falcon 9', 'RN Vostok'],
    correctAnswer: 'RN Vostok',
  },
];
